<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>book singing waiter tenors &#8211; Opera Singing Waiters Hire UK</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/book-singing-waiter-tenors/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/</link>
	<description>Fun and Fantastic Surprise Opera Performances!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 20:29:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.7.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/cropped-Hartley_voices_church_Singers-32x32.png</url>
	<title>book singing waiter tenors &#8211; Opera Singing Waiters Hire UK</title>
	<link>https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mark, tenor</title>
		<link>https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/singers/mark-tenor</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 13:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[operasingingwaiters]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Singers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[book singing waiter tenors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tenor singing waiters]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/?p=91</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Mark was born and bred in Cwmbran, South Wales. In 1995 he moved to Birmingham to study at the Conservatoire with the now head of vocal studies, Julian Pike, but never let go of his Welsh heritage. He gained a 1st Class Bachelor of Music Degree from the Birmingham Conservatoire in 1999. As a male &#8230; <a href="https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/singers/mark-tenor" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Mark, tenor"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/singers/mark-tenor">Mark, tenor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/">Opera Singing Waiters Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.funeralsingerhire.uk/2017/03/02/mark-tenor/mark_tenor/" rel="attachment wp-att-92"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-92" src="https://www.funeralsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Mark_tenor.jpg" alt="Mark, tenor for hire" width="177" height="229" /></a>Mark was born and bred in Cwmbran, South Wales. In 1995 he moved to Birmingham to study at the Conservatoire with the now head of vocal studies, Julian Pike, but never let go of his Welsh heritage. He gained a 1st Class Bachelor of Music Degree from the Birmingham Conservatoire in 1999. As a male Welsh singer, he gained a place on the Opera Course at The Guildhall School of Music and Drama Opera Course in London, studying with David Pollard and Rudolf Piernay.</p>
<p>He has worked extensively in the UK as a classical tenor, performing with such companies as: Grange Park Opera, English Touring Opera, Swansea City Opera, Garsington Opera, Savoy Opera, The D’Oyly Carte, Buxton Festival Opera, Opera Holland Park, Mid Wales Opera, Longborough Festival Opera and The Thursford Christmas Spectacular to name a few. In 2005 Mark understudied and played the role of Piangi in The Phantom of the Opera in London’s West End.</p>
<p>Mark was a finalist of the M.O.C.S.A. Young Welsh Singer of the Year competition three years running and also a finalist of the London Welsh Singer competition. He has worked with many Male Voice Choirs and Choral Society’s in Wales, including The Morrison and Orpheus, Bleanavon, Wrexham, Cwmbran and Tredeger MCV’s and Gala evenings with the Ammanford Choral and Pontypool Ladies Choir.</p>
<p>Mark has also performed many recitals in Britain, France and America. For the past two years Mark has performed at the fantastic Kilworth House Theatre in their “Last Night of the Proms” concert. He also helped open the theatre by being part of the inaugural cast for Kilworth’s Pirates of Penzance. In March 2009, for 14 months, Mark travelled the globe being part of the Production Cast, and also as a Guest Entertainer, for some of the biggest cruise liners in the world.</p>
<p>In April 2012 Mark played the role of Eddie (Donna Elvira) in a “gender swap” Don Giovanni for RC Productions staged at Heaven Nightclub in London’s West End. He received positive reviews both for his singing and portrayal of the role.</p>
<p>This year Mark played the role of MAÎTRE SUBTIL in “Fortunio” by Messager for Grange Park Opera. He is also returned to Longborough Festival Opera to take part once again in Wagners Götterdämmerung as a Vassel, and also returned to the International Gilbert and Sullivan Festival to take part in Iolanthe, Princess Ida and The Pirates of Penzance as a valued member of the professional company.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/singers/mark-tenor">Mark, tenor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.operasingingwaitershire.uk/">Opera Singing Waiters Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
